Hey.
嘿
God, I was so worried.
天哪 担心死我了
It's all right.
没事了啊
I thought you wouldn't come.
我以为你不会来了
It's okay now. Everything's going to be okay.
现在不就来了嘛 一切都会好的
Just tell me what's going on.
告诉我 怎么了
Wait.
等一下
We have to get out of here.
我们得离开这儿
No!
不
Danny... Oh, Danny...
Danny...哦 Danny...
No.
不
本字幕仅作学习交流之用 禁止用于任何商业用途 否则后果自负
==GA字幕组==
翻译:盼下雪的伯爵大人 教科书里的小华 K的伽利略 流年佳节胖三斤 lynhoo00 小末
校对：流年圣诞写论文 lynhoo00 蓉小张很低落 流年佳节胖三斤
字幕特效/时间轴：盼下雪的伯爵大人  压制：盼下雪的伯爵大人 军事顾问： Tom
It's just really short notice.
那个通知真的很短
How can you know if you don't ask?
如果你不问你怎么知道
It's not that simple. Doesn't get
-没那么简单 -没有
any simpler than that.
比那还要简单的了
Morning.
早上好
Got my parking space today.
我今天拿到停车位了
Oh.
哦
I mean, I-I know it's
我想说的是 我 我知道
only temporary, but it's right across the street
那只是暂时的 但它刚好在
from the building.
大楼对面的街上
At NSA, we park off-site, like, half a mile away.
在国家安全局 我们停在外面 有半英里远
God forbid you forgot anything.
千万别忘记任何东西（不然有得你走）
I took a picture.
我拍了张照
Want to see?
想看吗
Oh!
哦
Oh, it is a good spot.
哦 是个好地方
Nice.
不错
Delilah, by the way.
Delilah 顺便说下
Delilah... Fielding?
Delilah...Fielding
Really?
真的吗
I-I'm... I'm Ellie Bishop.
我 我 我是 Ellie Bishop.
I'm-I'm a huge fan.
我是你的粉丝
You are?!
你是
Yeah. Delilah's kind of a big deal in the analyst world, Tim.
是的 自从大头针放置行动之后
Ever since Operation Pin Drop.
Delilah就是分析界里的大人物了 Tim
Thank you. What's Operation Pin Drop?
-谢谢 -大头针放置行动是什么
Can't tell you.
不能告诉你
So, are you working here?
所以 你在这工作吗
No. Just trying to wrap something up with Tim.
不是 就是想和Tim聊一些东西
If by "something," you mean a classic case of Mcwaffling...
如果“一些东西” 你指的是Mcwaffaling经典案例
Well, how would you know...?
好吧 那么你是怎么知道的
- Tim butt-dialed me. - What?!
-Tim误拨电话给我了 -什么
Oh, my God.
哦 天哪
Well, it doesn't mean you have to listen.
那么 这并不是说 你必须得听
Oh, yes, it does. I find you compelling, Tim.
哦 是的 的确 我发现你好像很不情愿的样子 Tim
So, here's the deal.
所以 事情是这样的
Delilah's being awarded a fellowship
由于对反恐怖主义方面的工作
by the Conrad Institute for her work in counterterrorism.
Delilah被康拉德研究所授予了会员资格
Congrats, by the way. Thank you.
-恭喜你 顺便说一下 -谢谢
There's a black-tie gala event dinner.
【black-tie是对于晚宴的着装要求 正式程度仅次于白色领结 通常于下午六点后穿戴 男士着西装 女士裙子要齐膝】
有一个正式的庆祝晚宴
A who's who from the intel world.
一个来自情报世界默默无闻的人
Delilah wants
Deliha想
to bring McGee as her plus one.
让McGee做她的伴
But McGee's being McGee-- won't commit, waffling.
但是McGee就是McGee 不会随意许诺 优柔寡断
Did I leave anything out?
我有漏掉什么吗
- No, you summed it up. - Delilah,
-没有 你已经总结好了 -Deliha
I don't even own a tux.
我甚至都没有晚礼服
A case could come down at any moment.
随时会有案子
My boss is not big on time off.
老大对于休假没有热情
Who needs time off?
谁需要休假
McGee. Delilah's got a big shindig tomorrow night.
McGee Deliha明天晚上有个盛大的晚会要参加
No. No, I'm-I'm fine.
不是不是 我 我很好
What? You don't want to go?
什么 你不想去吗
Um... yeah, but...
恩 是的 但是...
Yeah, it's Gibbs.
是的 我是Gibbs
Grab your gear.
带上装备
We've got a dead sailor
我们有一个死了的海军
in Rock Creek Park.
在岩溪公园
Hey, don't use me as an excuse.
嘿 不要用我做借口
Petty Officer First Class Daniel Coyne.
上士丹尼尔·柯尼
Has $72 in his wallet
钱包里有72美元
and a gold watch which, according to the inscription,
和一个金表 根据注册信息
was a gift from his grandfather.
是他爷爷送的礼物
Not a robbery.
不是抢来的
It's a seven millimeter.
是7毫米（子弹）
Possible sniper round.
可能是狙击枪之类的
Indeed. So, our victim was shot by a high-powered rifle.
的确 那么 受害人被一支高能来福枪射中
And judging by the entrance and exit wounds,
从（子弹）进出的伤口可以判断出
at an extremely acute angle.
它是以一个极大的锐角（射入）
Suspect was in the trees?
嫌犯在树上
No.
不是
No, shooter was closer than that.
不是的 射击者比那要近
Yeah, and quite a bit higher.
是的 而且还要更高一点
...I walk my dog here every morning, like clockwork.
...我每天早上都在这里遛狗 分秒不差
Never seen anything like what happened today.
从来没有见过像天这样的事情
Can you describe what you saw?
你能描述下你所看到的吗
Oh, I can do you one better.
哦 我可以给你一个更好的
I can show you.
我可以给你看
You recorded it? Yes, sir.
-你录下了吗 -是的 先生
Right up here.
就在这里
Okay.
好的
I get it.
我懂了
So, how long exactly has the CIA been recording your thoughts
【此处为Tony对帽子男的讽刺】
所以 CIA通过你牙齿里那些填料
through the fillings in your teeth?
准确获取你的想法要多久
For six years, but they use microwaves.
六年了 但是他们用的是微波
Yeah. I've learned to be careful.
是的 我已经知道要小心点了
Now, let me tell you what happened.
现在 让我来告诉你发生了什么
A gray airship came down from the sky.
一个灰色的飞船从天上落下来
Killed that man.
杀了那个人
Bishop?
Bigshop
They were probably hunting me.
他们可能是在找我
Bishop, you want to hear this?
Bigshop 你想听到这个嘛
Captain Crazy-pants here has a little story
这位疯狂短裤船长有个小故事
he wants to tell us.
想告诉我们
Um, I don't think you're taking me seriously.
恩 我不认为你在认真对待我
Oh, no, I am.
哦 不 我很认真啊
Bishop's our expert on black helicopters. Shh.
Bigshop是我们在黑色直升机上的专家 嘘
No, it wasn't a helicopter.
不 那不是直升机
It was an airship.
那是一个飞船
And it was gray. Probably alien.
而且是灰色的 可能是外星人
Like this?
像这样
Yes, yes.
是的 是的
That's it. That's the one.
就是它 就是这个
He's not crazy.
他没疯
Other witnesses saw it, too.
其他目击者也见到它了
Wait a second.
等会
Are you telling me that an alien airship
你是在跟我说那是一个外星人飞船
came out of the sky and killed this man?
从天上冒出来 然后杀了这个人
Not alien. U.S. Navy.
不是外星人 美国海军
This is an Angelus surveillance drone.
这是一个Angelus无人侦察机
Someone used our own tech against us.
有人用我们自己的技术跟我们作对
Hey.
嘿
So, what's going on behind those sensitive green eyes, Tim?
那么 在这些敏感的嫉妒之眼后面发生了什么 Tim
Tony, I'm fine.
Tony 我很好
You think I can't see back there, but I can.
你以为我不能看见后面的地方 但是我能
You're insecure.
你有不安全感
That is not...
那不是...
Because you think maybe Delilah's too good for you?
因为你觉得 也许Delilah对你来说太好了
Out of your league?
配不上她
Who knows?
谁知道呢
But here's the thing, Tim.
但事实是 Tim
Man's reach should exceed his grasp...
一个人总是要不断超越自我
or what's a heaven for?
【这两句Tony引用了英国诗人 剧作家 罗伯特 勃朗宁的名言】
不然要天堂来做什么
Huh? Just something to think about.
啊 想想吧
Petty Officer Coyne was stationed at NAS Pax River.
【NAS: Naval Air Station 海军航空站】
Coyne上士在海军航空站的Pax河驻扎
A drone operator. Specialized in flying
一个无人机操控员
the same Angelus surveillance drone that killed him.
精通杀死他的Angelus无人侦察机飞行
Just spoke with his C.O. who's expecting us.
刚刚和他的指挥官谈过 他正指望我们呢
What's this?
这是什么
An analysis I wrote last year on the merits of drone warfare.
我去年做的关于无人机战争的优点分析
Redacted where necessary, but thorough enough as a primer
节选了必要的地方 但是在我们去Pax河前
on the subject before we head to Pax River.
作为这个话题的入门书 足够深入了
I don't need any primers on this subject, Bishop.
在这个话题上我不需要任何入门书 Bigshop
Here's where
这就是
I'm the expert. Oh, no.
-我精通的地方 -哦 不
I know what happens in a mechanized society
我知道在这个机械化的社会发生了什么
when mankind gets a little too complacent.
当人类得到一点点时 就太容易满足
Tony, please.
Tony 拜托
When his robot helpers rise up, seize power and overthrow us.
当他的机器人助手叛变 抢班夺权 然后推翻我们
What are you talking about?
你在说什么
Skynet.
【skynet来自于电影《终结者》以计算机为基础的人工智能防御系统 获得自我意识 并且认定人类是它存在的威胁 于是立刻倒戈对抗其创造者】
天网
No, I am not going down this rabbit hole again.
不 我不会再掉进这个陷阱里了
What's Skynet?
什么是天网
Skynet is a military computer designed to
天网就是一个
coordinate and control all our weapons systems,
为了协调和控制我们所有武器系统的军事计算机
including our nuclear arsenal,
包括我们的核军火库
until it turns on us
直到它攻击我们
and overthrows us.
消灭我们
So, this is a... movie?
这么说 这是一个...电影
Yeah. Terminator, one and two.
是的 终结者 第一部和第二部
Three and four don't count. No James Cameron.
【James Cameron 《终结者》导演 其他作品还有《泰坦尼克号》《阿凡达》】
第三第四部不算 没有詹姆斯·卡梅隆
Okay, uh, well, my research is in the actual use
好吧 额 那么 我的在无人机上的研究得到实际应用了
of Unmanned Aerial Vehicles, not the make-believe use.
不是一个让人相信的应用
And the bottom line is, UAVs save lives.
底线就是 无人机拯救了生命
Until they turn on us.
直到他们攻击我们以前
Okay, I guess that means you're not coming to Pax River.
好的 我猜 那就是说你不会来Pax河了
Oh, no.
哦 不
I am coming.
我会来的
Into the belly of the beast.
【史蒂文·西格尔主演电影】
潜入虎穴
What do you know, Duck?
你发现了什么 Duck
Well, if our petty officer's body
呃 如果我们上士的身体
is any indication, he was almost virtuous.
能说明什么的话 他几乎可以说是一个善良的人
Almost? There is a woman in his life.
几乎 在他的生活中有个女人
Well, last I heard, Duck, not a crime.
好吧 我听到的结尾 Duck 不是一个犯罪
Certainly not, but I would venture to guess
肯定不是 但是我会冒昧地猜一下
that she had very expensive tastes.
她的品味肯定很高
Take a whiff.
吸口气
Come on.
快点
Yeah...
是的
What do you smell? Chemicals.
你闻到了什么 化学药品
Yeah, but beyond the chemicals.
是的 但又不止化学品
Citrus, a note of bergamot.
柑橘 一个佛手柑的暗示
Ooh, the earthy aroma of iris.
鸢尾花泥土的香味
And beneath it all, vanilla.
全部在它下面 香草
Shalimar perfume, Jethro.
【Shalimar：Guerlain（娇兰）Shalimar（一千零一夜）属于全世界最经典香水之列】
一千零一夜香水 Jethro
Very exclusive.
很昂贵
$300 an ounce.
300美元一盎司
Above a petty officer's pay grade.
在上士的工资等级之上
I know all this
我知道这些
because I... I once had a dalliance
因为我 我 我曾经和
with a woman who a fondness for Shalimar.
一个喜欢一千零一夜香水的女人调过情
She had the most magnificent eyes.
她有最瑰丽的眼睛
There was little I wouldn't do when staring into those eyes.
当我盯着那些眼睛时 会做任何事
Geez, Duck-- what about the victim's girlfriend?
天哪 Duck --受害者的女朋友怎么样了
Uh... my examination showed
恩 我的检测表明
that the petty officer had intercourse
上士有过性交
shortly before his death.
就在他死之前
Whoever she is, she might know why he's ad.
不管她是谁 她可能知道他为什么被杀了
Yeah, cherchez la femme, Jethro.
是的 找出那个女人（法语）Jethro
Cherchez la femme.
找出那个女人
Lieutenant Commander Stone,
海军少校Stone
are any of your drones missing or inactive?
你的无人驾驶机当中有下落不明或者闲置的吗
Negative, ma'am. All birds accounted for.
没有 女士 所有飞机都算进去了
Well...
好吧
So, uh, any chance one of these
那么 嗯 有没有可能这其中
becoming, you know, sentient?
一架变得 你懂的 像人类一样有感知了
Every one of our drones requires an operator
我们这的每一架无人机都需要一个操作员
and several million dollars worth of software and equipment.
和价值几百万美金的软件和器材
They don't just,
他们不仅仅
uh, fly off on their own.
额 自己就能起飞
Anyone in your squadron capable of stealing one or modifying it?
你们空军中队有谁可以偷运或者改装它们吗
That would require a level of education and ability
那得需要一定水平的教育和能力
that so far surpasses anything they've demonstrated.
这远远超过了他们目前表现出来的能力
They are pilots.
他们是飞行员
These kids are barely out of high school.
这些小孩才刚刚离开高中
Their biggest risk is carpal tunnel.
【腕道症候群是职业伤害中最为常见的周边神经病变之一 尤其是需要重复手及腕部动作的职业】
他们最大的危险是腕道症候群
Not a fan of the post? Are you kidding?
-没人喜欢寄东西么 -开什么玩笑
I could run a full reconnaissance mission
我可以在地球上任何地方操作一个完整的侦查任务
anywhere in the world and still be home for dinner.
并且仍然可以在家吃晚饭
It's not too shabby.
这里一点也不寒酸
Just never thought
只是从未想到
I'd have to be a glorified hall monitor, too.
我也得当一个荣耀版的大厅监控器
What about Coyne? Was he a problem?
那Coyne呢 他有问题吗
Coyne was the exception.
Coyne例外
He's the only one in the squadron
他是中队中真正
who's actually flown missions.
执行过飞行任务的唯一一人
My number one trainer.
我的第一号助理教练
He had a bright future.
他本该有个光明的前程
Coyne was involved with a woman.
Coyne和一个女人有来往
Maybe the last person to see him alive.
可能是最后一个见到他活着的人
It's possible she's in the squadron?
她有可能是中队的人么
No, ma'am... it isn't.
不 女士 不可能
Come on, Commander.
别这样嘛 指挥官
You got a bunch of randy 20-year-olds
一群吵吵闹闹的20岁年轻人
running around here, hopped up on caffeine and candy bars.
在这里跑来跑去 对咖啡因和糖果店上瘾
May look like a, uh, college dorm out there,
或许你觉得这里有点像 嗯 大学宿舍
but this is still the U.S. Navy.
但这里仍然是美国海军部队
And there's absolutely no fraternizing in my squadron.
在我的中队绝对不可能有拉帮结派的
Danny's dead?
Danny死了
Coyne was seeing Petty Officer
Coyne当时和上士
First Class Patrice Gates.
Patrice Gates在交往
They bonded over a shared love
他们因为对爆米花和装修节目
for kettle corn and home improvement shows.
的共同喜爱而结识
He snuck into her quarters on a nightly basis,
他每晚都溜去她宿舍
and she flew his drone. Gates claims
她操作他的“机子”
they were getting married when her enlistment ended.
Gates声称他们本来准备等她服役结束后结婚
Claims?
声称
Well, Patrice has no appetite for the finer things in life.
嗯 Patrice对生活中的美好失去了兴趣
She buys her beauty supplies in bulk,
她买的美容产品都是散装的
and they don't sell Shalimar at the local Megamart.
【Megamart：澳大利亚连锁超市品牌】
当地的Megamart不卖一千零一夜香水
Coyne was knocking headboards with somebody else.
Coyne死前在和别人ooxx
Patrice Gates a suspect?
Patrice Gates是嫌疑人吗
She doesn't have a clue Coyne was cheating on her.
她并不知道Coyne有外遇
Or the technical know-how to operate a drone,
也不知道操作无人机的技术
let alone modify one into a weapon.
更不用说将无人机改造成为武器
Who does?
谁能呢
Only people familiar enough with the drone's system
那些熟知无人机操作系统的人
would be the contractors who built them.
可能会是制造无人机的承包商
Okay. Let's talk to 'em.
好 我们去找他们谈谈
Well, that's gonna be a bit of a problem.
嗯 这会是个问题
See, the company is Reinhart-Carion.
制造无人机系统的公司是Reinhart-Carion
I went to go run a background check
我去查他们雇员的背景资料
on their employees and was turned away.
但被拒绝了
Turns out Reinhart-Carion is already under investigation
【DOD：Department of Defense 国防部】
原来国防部已经对Reinhart-Carion公司
by the DoD.
展开调查了
Whoever is running that investigation,
无论谁在查
I want them in here.
我要他们到这来谈谈
Delilah...?
Delilah
This is not a good time.
现在不方便呢
I'm not here to see you.
我不是到这里来看你的
Then who?
那是找谁
Me.
我
If that's okay with you, Special Agent McGee.
如果你没什么异议的话 特别探员McGee
Gibbs, you, too.
Gibbs 你也来
Drone strike six months ago in Pakistan wilderness.
无人机六个月前对巴基斯坦荒地发动袭击
Terrorist camp belonging to
恐怖分子的大本营属于
Benham Parsa. Our response for the bombing
Benham Parsa 也就是去年
that killed SECNAV last year.
海军部长被炸身亡的元凶
Mission was a success, though Parsa escaped.
任务是顺利完成了的 不过Parsa逃走了
What's this got to do with my dead petty officer?
这和那个死了的上士有什么关系呢
Coyne was part of the kill chain.
Coyne是杀人链的一部分
He flew the Angelus surveillance drone
他操作Angelus无人监察机
that positively confirmed Parsa was present.
上面明确显示Parsa在现场
His UAV went down during the strike--
他的无人机在袭击中被击落
mechanical failure.
机械故障
Defense believes
国防部的认为
that Parsa or his people may have recovered
Parsa或者他的人有可能修复了
the UAV, smuggled it stateside.
那架无人机 偷运到美国国内
And used it against Coyne as retaliation for this attack?
然后用来报复Coyne
There's been chatter for days he's making a move in the U.S.
小道消息说他要在美国开始行动了
You and I both know Parsa's not gonna go through
你和我都知道Parsa不会仅仅因为要杀一个人
all this trouble just to kill one man.
就要这么折腾
There'll be more attacks.
肯定还有更多的恐怖袭击
Yes.
是的
Director, I need to speak
主任 我需要和Gibbs通话
with Gibbs. It's McGee.
我是McGee
Hey.
嗨
Did you find the DoD investigator?
你找到了国防部的调查员了吗
Not exactly.
不全是
Before I could, she found us.
在我行动之前 她先找到我们了
Boss, I had no idea.
老大 我完全不知情
If I did, I would've warned you.
如果我知道 我一定会提醒你的
Warned me about what?
提醒我什么
About me.
关于我
Hey, Jethro.
嗨 Jethro
It's not another one of your ex-wives, is it?
她该不是你的前妻之一吧
Close enough.
差不多了
You two know each other?
你俩认识
Uh-huh.
对啊
It's been a few years.
已经有几年了吧
Why are you here,
你为什么在这里
Hollis? I was brought on
-Hollis -我曾被国防部
by the DoD to run an internal investigation
派到Reinhart-Carion公司
- into Reinhart-Carion. - The defense contractors
-去执行一项内部调查 -这些国防承包商
who built and maintain the drones at NAS
负责在海军航空站建造和维护无人机
- Pax River? Mm-hmm.
-Pax河 -是的
Reinhart's computer systems were hacked.
Reinhart的电脑系统被黑了
When? A month ago.
-什么时候 -一个月前
And you kept this to yourself. That would be
-你没上报 -因为这是一个
the definition of "internal," Jethro.
内部调查 Jethro
It's...
我们认为
our belief that a Navy Angelus UAV
海军Angelus无人机
was compromised, rewired and used to kill a U.S. drone pilot.
被盗用 重新编写程序 然后被用来谋杀了一个美国无人机飞行员
- By who? - Nah.
-谁做的 -不
You first.
你先说
Any suspects on your theft? We have...
-你这有什么嫌疑人吗 -我们有
one suspect.
一个嫌疑人
A Reinhart employee.
一个Reinhart的雇员
Erin Pace.
Erin Pace
She's a highly trained computer programmer and engineer.
她是一个经过高强度训练的电脑程序员和工程师
She's been MIA for several days--
【MIA：Missing In Action 在任务中失踪】
她执行任务时失踪 好几天了
not at work, not at home,
没上班 也没在家
and she's absolutely capable of reconfiguring a drone
她绝对有能力重新配置一架无人机
in the way you describe.
就像你描述的那样
Your turn.
该你说了
Okay.
好
We'll get back to you.
我们还会来找你的
That's not the deal.
当时说好的不是这样
Didn't make a deal.
我没有约定过什么
This is my investigation.
这是我的调查
It was.
以前是
Now it's mine.
现在是我的了
I was appointed by the inspector general to see it through.
检察长委派我搞定这件事
Don't make me go above your head.
别逼我去找你上司
Hollis, my boss is right here.
hollis 我的上司就在这呢
Keep me out of it. I'm talking
-别扯上我 -我在和
about his boss and his boss's boss.
他的上司和他上司的上司协商
I've got them all on speed dial.
我把他们都放在了快速拨号里
We need to work together,
我们需要合作
however hard that might be for you.
不管这对你来说有多难
No. Not gonna happen.
不 这不可能
Hollis Mann.
Hollis Mann
Yep. They're being, uh, resistant.
是的 他们都在 呃 拒绝合作
You sure she's not an ex-wife, Gibbs?
Gibbs 你确定她不是你前妻
He'd like to speak with you.
他想跟你谈谈
This is Vance.
我是Vance
Yes, Mr. Secretary.
是的 部长先生
A joint investigation.
联合调查
Understood.
我明白
Yes, sir. Thank you.
是的 长官 谢谢
That was the Secretary of Defense.
是国防部长的命令
She's in, Gibbs.
她得加入了 Gibbs
Hollis Mann.
Hollis Mann
What does it mean?
意味着什么
Uh, we still have a dead petty officer and a missing drone.
呃 我们手上还有个死掉的海军下士和失踪的无人机
Shouldn't we be, you know, investigating?
我们是不是 你懂的 继续调查
This is our process, Bishop.
这是例行程序  Bishop
You have your earbuds and chess metaphors.
你有你的耳塞和象棋比喻
We have this; don't knock it.
我们有这个 请勿打扰
Besides, Gibbs and Hollis are probably
还有啊 估计Gibbs和Hollis
up there arguing over jurisdiction.
正为谁管辖的问题争论呢
Their version of foreplay.
这就是他们的前戏模式
So, who is Hollis Mann?
谁是Hollis Mann
Penetrating question, Bishop.
相当尖锐的问题 Bishop
She was supposed to be Gibbs' fourth ex-wife.
她应该是Gibbs的第四任前妻
Fourth?
第四任
How many does he have?
他到底有几个
Well, there was only the one real wife.
实际上是只有一个真正意义上的妻子
Then there's the exes.
剩下的都是前妻
Keep it simple, McGee. Exes only.
不要说得那么复杂 McGee 只是前妻们而已
Let's do the thing.
我们开始吧
All right.
好吧
On three.
数到三
When I give you the all clear.
等我给你们安全提示
Coast is clear. Let's do this.
没有危险 开始吧
One, two, three. Put it up.
一 二 三 放到屏幕上
Ex-wife number one, Diane.
前妻1号 Diane
Satan's spawn, first sign of the apocalypse.
撒旦再世 天启的第一迹象
You've met her. Tim slept with her.
你见过她 Tim还和她睡过
Emphasis on "slept." Then there's Stephanie,
重点在睡"过" 接下来是Stephanie
ex number three.
前妻3号
She matches Diane in personality and charm.
她在个性和魅力方面与Diane不相上下
What about ex-wife number two?
前妻2号呢
Total mystery. Don't even have a name.
完全是个谜 甚至连名字都没有
Sort of a Gibbsian Bermuda Triangle.
类似于Gibbs百慕大三角关系
And Hollis Mann?
那Hollis Mann呢
That's the one that got away.
这是唯一一个逃出三角关系的
Gibbs met her on a case.
Gibbs在办一个案子时认识的她
Army CID. Total pro.
【Army CID：Criminal Investigation Department 陆军犯罪调查司令部】
陆军犯罪调查司令部 各方面都很专业
And no discernible personality disorders.
没有明显的人格缺陷
Pretty soon it was late nights down in the basement,
在深夜的地下室中 奸情迅速发展
looking good and then...
看起来不错 然后...
Hollis... gone.
Hollis...离开了
She retired from the Army. Moved to Hawaii.
她从部队退役后搬去了夏威夷
We read about it in Stars and Stripes.
我们从《星条旗报》上看到的
【星条旗报：美国军方报纸】
No harassing phone calls, no Viking funerals, just...
没有撒泼上吊 没有死缠烂打 只是...
gone.
简简单单地走了
They broke up, clearly.
很显然是分手了
No, there's no way of knowing.
不清楚 无法通过任何途径了解详情
There's one way. You could just ask.
有个方法 你可以直接问
Ask me what?
问我什么
Hi. Uh, yeah.
嘿 呃 是的
No, nothing. I could.
没 没什么 我可以
Why don't you call me back?
你为什么不回电
Erin Pace.
Erin Pace
May be involved in the drone attack.
可能和这个袭击有关
Locate her.
找到她
Um... Benham Parsa? Right?
-嗯... -Benham Parsa 对吗
Yeah? What do you know about him?
是吗 关于他你知道些什么
Uh...  um...
呃...嗯...
uh, what do you... what do you need?
呃 你需要...需要了解些什么
Early life and education?
早年间的生活还是教育情况
Uh, radicalization?
呃 政治观点
Current activities and correspondence...
实际行事还是通信来往
All of it.
所有的
Oh, hey, Gibbs. I heard. She's back.
哦 嘿 Gibbs 我听说 她回来了
Does she look the same? Did you guys get to talk?
她有没有什么变化 你们聊天了吗
Was it totally awkward?
还是尴尬的面对面
It is now.
现在就尴尬了
Oh...
噢...
Hey there...
原来你在这啊...
You could've told me, Gibbs. Didn't give me a chance, Abbs.
你应该提醒我的 Gibbs 你都没给我机会说 Abbs
It's good to see you, Abby. It's good to see you, too.
很高兴见到你 Abby 我也很高兴见到你
I'm just gonna, uh, take my foot
我得把我惹祸的嘴闭上
out of my mouth so we can talk about what I've got.
然后再说我在案子上的发现
Yes. I had my office forward you the evidence we pulled
是的 我已经通过办公室
from Erin Pace's apartment.
把我们在Erin Pace公寓发现的证据交给了你
Every hairbrush and coffee cup and paper clip that she owned.
甚至还有她的牙刷 咖啡杯和纸巾
We like to be thorough. You find anything?
-我们做事细致 -你有什么发现吗
I found Shalimar perfume.
我发现了娇兰一千零一夜系列香水
It matches the traces that Ducky found on Coyne's skin.
和Ducky在Coyne皮肤上发现的气味相同
Wait, your victim was sleeping with my suspect?
等等 你的受害人和我的嫌疑人上过床
Or at least involved in some very heavy petting.
或者说至少有很密切的接触行为
But I also found this.
但是我还发现了这个
Orange juice? Yep.
-橙汁 -是的
I already had my people run it for prints.
我已经让我的人对指纹进行对比了
Only found Pace's. I, too, like to be very thorough,
-只找到了Pace的 -我也是个挺细心的人
so I swabbed the spout for DNA. Got a hit.
我在瓶口提取了DNA 找到了匹配者
Meet... Yusef Ryder.
就是... Yusef Ryder
He served multiple sentences at multiple prisons
他因为多种犯罪背叛数个刑罚
for multiple violent crimes.
分别在不同的地方服刑
He was most recently an inmate at Jessup
目前应该在
Correctional Institution,
Jessup监狱服刑
where he officially converted to Islam.
并正式皈依伊斯兰教
I mean, he sounds just like
我的意思是 他看起来
the kind of guy that Benham Parsa would love to recruit.
就像会被Benham Parsa招募进来的人
He doesn't exactly have the background
他并无任何
to operate and maintain a drone.
操作和驾驶无人机的经历
No, but he does have a background
是的 但他却擅长
in kidnapping and aggravated assault.
绑架和严重袭击
What, you think that he coerced Erin Pace?
你认为是他强迫了Erin Pace
I think if we find him, we find out.
我觉得只要找到他 问题便迎刃而解
Yusef Ryder skipped parole two weeks ago,
Yusef Ryder两周前被保释
dropped off the map until Monday,
然后失踪直到周一
when he was caught on video camera robbing a gun store.
再次捕捉到他的影像就是他持枪抢劫一个枪械商店
Grabbed a small arsenal,
发现了一个小型军火库
including a high-powered rifle that matches
里面的大型杀伤力步枪
the make and model used to kill Coyne.
和杀死Coyne的步枪型号相匹配
Fled in a stolen van.
并且偷了一辆面包车
We put out a BOLO.
我们发了通缉令
Virginia State troopers spotted it
弗吉尼亚的警察大约在十分钟前
at a motel parking lot near Falls Church
于福尔斯彻奇市附近
about ten minutes ago.
一家汽车旅馆的停车场发现了他
They're babysitting till we get there.
在我们到达之前他们负责监控
Let's roll.
我们出发
Manager said that Yusef checked in two days ago,
管理员说Yusef是两天前用假身份证
using an assumed identity.
登记入住的
Room's in the back.
房间在后面
McGee and I are gonna check it out now.
McGee和我进去搜查
Got eyes on the van.
你注意那辆面包车
All right, we need to talk.
好的 我们需要谈谈
About what?
谈什么
About this.
就现状
You haven't said a word to me since we got in the car, Jethro.
自从坐上车你没跟我说过一句话 Jethro
It's been six years.
已经六年了
You must have something to say.
你肯定有什么话要说
No. No, I'm good.
不 没有 我很好
Hmm.
哼
You want to talk, you should ride with DiNozzo.
你要是想聊天 就应该坐DiNozzo的那辆车
How was Hawaii?
夏威夷怎么样
It was beautiful.
很漂亮
And... boring.
也...有些无聊
Hmm.
唔
Only so many perfect days a woman can take.
是一个女人所拥有的最美好的时光
I... just had to get back to work.
我...只是回来工作而已
I got married.
我结婚了
Mm-hmm.
唔
That happens. No, it's not like that.
我猜到了 不 不是你想的那样
He's a good guy. He's...
他是个好人
a doctor at Walter Reed.
他是Walter Reed医院
Trauma surgeon. I...
的创伤外科医生 我...
met him two years ago, right after I got back.
两年前遇到他 就在我回来之前
I would have called you, but I...
我曾想过要打电话给你 但我...
Yeah...
是的
you're right. Silence is better.
你说的没错 沉默才是该有的气氛
Room's empty, Gibbs, but the van just started moving.
房间是空的 Gibbs 但是面包车发动了
Ten bucks says he didn't get far.
打赌十块钱 他肯定跑不远
No.
必须的
Not far.
肯定不远
Yusef Ryder!
Yusef Ryder
Federal agents!
我们是联邦探员
You're okay,
你没事了
and you are safe.
也安全了
I'm not. I'm not safe.
不 我一点都不安全
None of us are.
我们都身处危险
He kidnapped me,
他绑架了我
took me to this storage building.
带我去了一个在建的仓库
There were other men.
那里还有其他人
How many? Three.
有几个 三个
Maybe more.
也许还有更多
Pakistani.
是巴基斯坦人
One of them spoke English.
其中一个人说英语
He was different.
他跟其他人不同
He spoke perfectly.
他的英语非常地道
Like, proper English, almost British.
应该是英国人
Um... polite.
很有礼貌
Almost reasonable, like he was
讲话逻辑条理分明 貌似他站在
on my side.
我这边
He had an Angelus UAV.
他有一架Angelus无人机
They wanted you to modify it.
他们需要你来改装
I refused...
我一开始
at first.
拒绝了
Then, uh,
然后 呃
the polite one pulled out a laptop with a live video feed.
那个有礼貌的男人拿出一台
It was my husband,
视频直播的电脑
asleep in bed.
视频里是我丈夫在床上睡觉
He works for an NGO in Mali.
他在马里的非政府组织工作
Somehow they had a camera on him.
肯定有人在监视他
I did everything they said after that.
然后我就照着他们说的做了
And Petty Officer Coyne?
你和Coyne下士
Were you close?
很熟悉吗
No, we worked together.
不 我们只是一起工作而已
They forced me to get him to the park.
他们逼我带他去公园
You were the bait.
你就是诱饵
Yeah.
是的
I-I didn't mean to get...
我不是有意要...
I mean, I never would, uh...
我是说 我从没想...
I did... I-I didn't have a choice.
我...我别无选择
Erin, no one's saying you did.
Erin 没有人责怪你
Coyne's murder was a test run.
谋杀Coyne仅仅是一起试运行
Who's next?
谁是下一个目标
Someone important-- I heard them whispering about it.
应该是个重要人物 我听到他们低声讨论过
Something about...
大致上是有关巴基斯坦的
revenge for an attack in Pakistan.
一次袭击的报复行动
It was hard to make out, but...
他们的交谈很难听清  但是
I picked up a word.
我还是听到了一个词
It didn't make much sense.
但这个词没有什么太大的意义
Acrobat.
杂技演员
Acrobat?
Are you sure?
你确定么
It's a Secret Service
这是特勤局
code name for Joint Base Andrews.
给安德鲁斯空军基地编的代号
Erin, I-I know you're tired.
Erin 我知道你现在很累
But I need to ask you about this man,
但我需要问你些关于那个男人的情况
uh, the polite one?
呃 那个文雅点的男人
Is this him?
你看是他么
Benham Parsa
is in the country?
到这个国家了
That's what Erin Pace said.
Erin Pace是这么说的
How do you know it was him?
你怎么知道就是他呢
The way Erin described him, uh...
Erin是这样描述他的
soft-spoken, proper English, good manners.
谈吐温和 口音地道 彬彬有礼
All habits he picked up in the international school he attended.
这些生活习惯都是他在国际学校就读时学到的
Why did he come? We used a Hellfire missile
-他为什么来 -我们用地狱火导弹
to destroy his compound in Pakistan.
摧毁了他在巴基斯坦的大本营
Maybe he feels safer here.
估计他觉得这里更安全
- He's not. - Secretary of Defense
-他不会这么想 -国防部长
is scheduled to meet with several world leaders
已经安排明日在安德鲁斯海军基地
at Joint Base Andrews tomorrow.
会见几位其他国家领导人
Hollis Mann is coordinating with Secret Service
Hollis Mann已经配合特勤局
to relocate that event. Parsa doesn't know that.
重新布置明天的活动  Parsa应该还没收到消息
Gives us a day to track him and the stolen UAV.
这就给了我们一天的时间追踪他和那架无人机的下落
Go to it.
去做吧
Delilah. Hey.
Delilah 嘿
You here to see Director Vance again?
你又来见Vance主任了
No. You, this time.
不是 这次是来见你的
Brought you something.
给你带了点东西
What is it?
这是什么
Tuxedo.
晚礼服
I know you don't have one.
我知道你还没有
It's really nice.
这身真的很不错
Look, Delilah...
是这样的 Delilah
Oh, I know you can't come.
哦 我知道你不能去
Parsa's out there, national security, I get it.
Parsa还在逃 涉及国家安全 我理解
Can't return the tux, though,
即便如此 也不能退货
I already had it tailored.
我都照着你的身材改好了
How'd you get my sizes?
你怎么知道我的尺寸
I'm a cryptologist for the Department of Defense,
我可是国防部的密码破译专家
I think I can figure out my boyfriend's inseam.
我应该能计算出我男朋友的内接缝要怎么缝
Delilah.
Delilah
I'm sorry, okay?
我真的很抱歉
No, I understand, Tim. I do.
不 我理解 Tim 我能理解
This is important.
眼下的事很重要
But I know you never really wanted
但我也知道你从未真心想
to come to the gala with me.
和我一起去晚宴
And that I just can't understand.
这才是我不能理解的地方
No.
不对
No, this is wrong.
不对 大错特错
Well, you said diet. Not the soda. Parsa, it...
你说了你要无糖的  -不是说汽水 是Parsa
- it's too small for him. - Too small?
这对他而言规模太小 -规模小
He smuggled a remote control assassin into the country
他走私了一架可远程遥控的暗杀者进入这个国家
to pick off international VIPs.
想要摆平那些国际要员
He's a blunt instrument, not a surgeon.
他向来是如钝器攻击般直接了当 可不是外科医生般谨小慎微
He doesn't whisper, h-he... he bellows.
他的活动从不是低声细语型  而是大声怒吼型
Cairo, 2007. He detonated
开罗 2007年 他引爆了一颗
a bomb inside a passenger train.
安装在客运火车内的炸弹
Killed 30.
死了30人
The Indian Ocean, 2008.
印度洋 2008年
He sabotaged a French cargo ship-- 15 dead.
他破坏了一艘法国货轮 15人死亡
Bahrain, two years ago. He took 20 people
巴林岛 两年前
hostage inside a luxury hotel. He-he killed them all.
他在一家豪华酒店劫持了20名人质并杀死了所有人
Got to be a hoot at parties. Parsa doesn't go to parties.
他肯定会是派对里最有趣的人  Parsa根本不参加派对
He doesn't drink, smoke, date-- h-he spends all of his time
他不嗜酒 不抽烟 不约会 他把所有时间都用在
planning and executing his attacks. Okay.
-策划和执行他的恐怖袭击上了 -好吧
Why don't we all just take a deep breath.
为什么我们不先喘口气缓一缓
We can work with what we have.
我们可以搞定手头上的这些信息
Which is a multi-million dollar Navy robot
造价数百万的海军机器人
the size of a car-- can't be all that easy fly, let alone hide.
和汽车差不多大  可不是那么容易就飞起来的 更不必说把它藏起来
Designed for stealth, flies under the radar.
专为秘密行动设计 能逃过雷达监控
Could be stored in a garage.
可能会被藏在车库
Got to be a way to trace it.
应该会是一个追查的方向
They're usually operated from halfway around the world
操作这些机器通常需要使用地球另一端的
using military satellites.
军用卫星
Parsa doesn't have those kind of resources.
Parsa可没有这种资源
No, and that's why he had
是的 这就是他为什么让
Erin Pace rewire it.
Erin Pace重新连线的原因
He doesn't need it to be long range,
他不需要那么大的攻击范围
he's close by, which means piggybacking off a local system.
他就在附近 这就意味着他黑了当地系统
I can work with that.
我能解决那个问题
He can work with that.
他能解决那个问题
The world as we know it
正如我们所知道的
is falling apart all around us...
即使我们身处的这个世界分崩离析
and you're down here.
你也依旧在你的地下室待着
I'm not at all surprised.
我真是一点也不惊讶
I brought dinner.
我带来了晚饭
I already ate.
我已经吃过了
In that case...
那么
dessert.
饭后甜点
Small batch.
威士忌
Very smooth.
非常好喝
Thank you.
谢谢
It's been a long time since I've been down in this basement.
从我上次来到这个地下室 已经过去了很久
I miss the boat.
我想念那艘船
Kind of pulled the whole room together.
好像把这个屋子都填满
What are you doing?
你在干什么
I'm trying to make peace.
我只是想要表现得友好
We're good. What are you doing?  Good?
-我们很好 你到底在做什么  -很好
Really? Because it kind of feels
真的么  因为这感觉起来
the exact opposite.
正好有点相反
What do you want from me, Hollis?
Hollis 你想从我这里得到什么
I want to apologize.
我想要道歉
There's no need.
没有这个必要
Oh, stop that.
噢 算了吧
God, I forgot how
我都忘了你是
infuriating you could be.
多么容易令人发怒了
Was that the apology?
这就是你的道歉么
No.
不是
No, this is. I...
不是 这 我...
I liked you, okay?
我喜欢过你 对么
I really liked you.
我真的喜欢过你
And what happened between us, it was good.
我们之间发生的事情很美妙
It was great, even.
甚至可以说非常棒
But there was a wall that wasn't coming down.
但是我们之间总好像隔着一堵墙
Your past.
你的过去
And I could see what was gonna happen.
我能看到将会发生什么
How bad it was gonna get.
事情会有多坏
Me, trying to... pull things from you,
我试着让你忘掉这些过去
and you not ready to let go.
但你还没有做好放手的准备
So I made an executive decision-- I left...
所以我做了一个决定 离开
...so that...
所以
we could remember the good.
我们能记住我们之间那些美好的事情
You should have just asked.
你应该直接告诉我的
I'm sorry, Jethro.
对不起 Jethro
Hey, hey...
嗨 嗨
With Parsa's piggybacking
由于Parsa的黑了
off of local radio towers,
当地的无线电天线塔
it'll be low-frequency, low-volume providers.
它会是一个低频率 小容量的提供商
I checked every college radio station
我检查了每一所大学里的无线电台
in DC, Virginia and Maryland.
华盛顿 弗吉尼亚和马里兰
Well, we still got to keep looking.
好吧 我们需要继续寻找
So...
所以
Delilah.
Delilah
Not you, too.
怎么你也来问我
Ugh.
唉
Look, I didn't have a choice.
听着 我没有其它的选择
I can't go to the awards gala with her.
我不能去参加颁奖晚宴
I feel bad, okay? It just...
-我感觉不好 -看起来
seemed like you...
像是你...
didn't really want to go.
不是真的想去
I didn't.
我没有
McGee!
McGee
I thought you really liked her!
我认为你真的喜欢她
I did.
是的
I do.
我喜欢
We're together all the time,
我们在一起的时光
which is nice.
都是那么美好
We went on a trip together.
我们曾一起旅行
She leaves clothes at my apartment.
她把衣服留在我家
She bought me a tuxedo.
她给我买了晚礼服
I mean, that's a little much, don't you think? Too much.
我的意思是她为我做的太多了 你不觉得吗 太多了
I think I just need to slow things down.
我认为我需要缓慢速度
I need... space.
我需要...空间
Hey. Oh, boo-hoo.
-嘿 -哦 呸呸
"My super-hot, super-smart girlfriend
我的超级火辣、超级漂亮的女朋友
likes me too much?"
太喜欢我了
McGee, this is not about space.
McGee 这不是空间的问题
It's about you being scared.
这是你自身的恐惧
You're scared that things aren't going to work out,
你害怕事情解决不了
and somebody's gonna get hurt,
以及有人会受伤
and then you have to deal with those
然后你不得不处理这些
messy emotions.
复杂的情感
Delilah is, like, the best thing
Delilah就仿佛是
that's ever happened to you.
你身边从未出现过的最好的礼物一样
You can't protect yourself from everything.
你不能只顾着保护自己
Oh, picking up something here.
哦 这里得到些线索
A signal from the Emergency Broadcast System tower.
来自应急广播系统塔的信号
The EBS is always emitting a signal.
应急广播系统塔总是发射信号
Yeah, but this is a second carrier wave,
是的 但这是第二载波
it's not broadcasting anything.
不传播任何信号
Do you have the signal origin?
你有原始信号吗
Triangulating.
三角测量中
Looks like some kind of
看上去像是一些
storage building.
仓库类的建筑物
Just like Erin Pace described.
正如Erin Pace描述的那样
Got eyes on Yusef; no sign of the others.
-看到Yusef了 没有其他人
We take the drone, we take Yusef.
拿下Yusef 就等于掌握了无人机的情况
Alive, if possible.
要活的 如果可以的话
He's our link to Parsa.
他是我们抓住Parsa的线索
You stick to DiNozzo.
你紧跟DiNozzo
I aced tactical weapons training,
我接受过战术武器训练
I can take care of myself.
我可以照顾自己
I know, Bishop. Stick to DiNozzo.
我知道 Bishop 紧跟DiNozzo
Stick to me.
跟着我
NCIS!
海军罪案调查处
Whoa...
哇...
Lucky shot?
秒杀
My first time. M-My first time I fire a weapon.
我第一次 我第一次开枪
I mean, most agents never even fire a weapon in anger.
我意思是 大多数探员都未曾在愤怒中开枪
Me, I blow up a building.
我 我炸毁了一幢房子
Well, it was...
好吧 那只是...
kind of a smallish building.
一个比较小的仓库
Do you know how much trouble I'm in?
你知道我惹了多大麻烦吗
Forget the fact I took out a multimillion-dollar Navy drone,
我毁掉了价值亿万美元的海军无人机 这个事实暂时不提
I... I killed our one link to Parsa.
我...我还杀了抓住Parsa的唯一线索
No.
不
You didn't.
你没有
This did. What?
-这个才是元凶 -什么
It's the detonator
这根雷管
that set off the explosives inside the storage building.
引爆了仓库里的炸药
It's probably C-4-- it'll take me some time to confirm.
炸药很可能是C-4 需要花一些时间去确认
Yusef martyred himself?
Yusef自己要寻死
And you did your job.
而你只是做了你的工作
Well, we're still no closer to finding Parsa.
好吧 但我们始终没有找到能够抓住Parsa的线索
Come on.
过来
- You're a puzzle solver. - Oh, this...
-你是个解谜者 -哦 这
isn't like any other puzzle I've ever solved.
不同于其他任何我已经解决的谜团
That's why you just have to stay organized.
这就是为什么你必须有组织地行事
Um, so I've split all this stuff up into quadrants.
嗯 所以我把所有东西都拆分成象限
The first one is bomb components,
第一部分是炸弹零件
the second one is drone parts,
第二部分是无人机残骸
and the third is just miscellaneous.
第三部分是各种混杂的部分
Ah, thanks.
啊 谢谢
Okay, so, like this, this would be
好的 然后 像这个 这是
our left wing thruster
无人机上的
from our Angelus UAV.
左翼推进器
McGee!
McGee
You look like the top of a wedding cake.
你看起来像新郎一样
Thank you, I think. So you're going
谢谢你 那么你决定出席
to the Conrad gala?
Conrad晚宴
Well, the immediate threat
嗯 眼前恐怖袭击的
of a terror attack is over.
威胁已经解除
I know Delilah wants me there, so I'm going.
我知道Delilah希望我去，所以我决定去
I would hug you so much right now, if I weren't...
我真想给你个拥抱 如果我身上没有...
covered in hazardous materials.
沾满危险材料
Abby, thank you.
Abby 谢谢你
Okay, next piece.
好了，下一部分
This one...
这部分...
...is also the left wing thruster.
...也是左翼推进器
What are you telling me, Abby?
你要告诉我什么 Abby
We went through each and every part, Gibbs.
我们已经检查过每个部分 Gibbs
There's two left thrusters, a couple of rusted-out axles,
这是两个左翼推进器 一对生锈的轮轴
and a mangled motherboard-- I mean, none of it connects.
和一块损坏的主板 我意思是 它们之间没有任何联系
It's spare parts.
这些都是备用零件
It's, like, pieces from old drones
就好像 旧的无人机上的一块块旧零件
that have been decommissioned for years.
已经报废了好多年了
The serial numbers don't even match each other,
这一连串数据之间甚至都不匹配
let alone the Angelus that went down in Pakistan.
更不用说在巴基斯坦被击落的Angelus无人机了
The C-4 from the storage unit, it was supposed to go off.
仓库的C-4炸弹 应该被引爆
The trigger from the bomb
炸弹引爆器
used a radio signal. Yusef probably
使用无线电信号 Yusef可能
meant to set the bomb off after he left,
打算离开后再引爆炸弹
but changed his mind when he saw he was cornered.
然而当他发现自己已被逼入绝境时他改变了主意
Parsa wanted us to think that the drone was destroyed.
Parsa想让我们认为无人机被毁灭了
So the drone's still out there.
然而无人机仍然在那里出没
Yeah, Ducky?
是的 Ducky
Our victim is not what he seems, Jethro.
我们的受害人并非我们看到的那样 Jethro
Yeah, been hearing that a lot lately.
是的 最近听说了好多
When I was examining him just now, I noticed
刚才在我解剖他的时候 我注意到
a crescent moon tattoo on his palm.
他手掌的新月纹身
The crude design and improvised metallic ink
粗糙的设计和简易的金属油墨
suggest that it was acquired in prison.
表明这是在监狱中纹的
A symbol of his conversion to Islam.
这是伊斯兰教的象征
Yes, but it also piqued my interest in his other tattoos.
是的 但他身上其他的纹身也激起了我的兴趣
This dagger here represents La Vida Mala,
这个匕首代表La Vida Mala
and this one percent tat on his arm
他手臂上这个百分之一的纹身
with the Vandals Motorcycle Club,
代表Vandals摩托车俱乐部
and several other unpleasant organizations.
以及其他三流组织的纹身
Yusef got around. Well, it all suggests
-Yusef到处辗转 -好吧 这一切都表明
that this man was quite mercenary
在他参加的组织中
in his affiliations,
他唯利是图
joining all these groups
参加所有这些组织
not for philosophic reasons,
并不出于哲学原因
but because they offered protection in prison,
而是因为这些组织在监狱提供保护
and employment on the outside.
在外面提供就业
Yusef here is a survivor.
Yusef是一个生存意识极强的人
Not the type of man willing to martyr himself for a cause.
他并不是一个愿意为了目标能自我牺牲的人
Not a suicide bomber.
那并不是一个自杀式炸弹
Precisely.
对
Someone else detonated the bomb
有人引爆了
at the storage facility. Mm-hmm.
仓库里的炸弹 -嗯
Parsa played us.
Parsa耍了我们
Well, Benham Parsa is the type of man
是的 Benham Parsa是一个
who revels in deceit and misdirection.
以欺骗和误导别人为乐的人
Nothing is ever what it seems.
我们看到的 都仅仅是表象
Why am I
为什么我
in an interrogation room?
在审讯室里
Main objective is to unsettle you.
主要目的是动摇你
Okay... well, it-it's working.
-好了... -好吧 现在开始了
Terrific. How's your marriage?
好极了 你的婚姻生活如何
I... It's fine.
我...很好
You helped America's most wanted terrorist
你帮助美国头号通缉的恐怖分子
design a weapon because your husband was being threatened.
设计武器是因为你的丈夫被威胁了
I hope your marriage is doing a little better than fine.
我希望你的婚姻比起很好来更好一点
- It's good, all right? - You haven't seen
-非常好 好吗 -你已经有十一个月都没有见过
your husband in 11 months.
你的丈夫
Well, he works overseas.
是的 他在海外工作
You haven't spoken, e-mailed, Facebook'd
你从没和他有过交谈 电邮 微博
or even written a postcard.
甚至写明信片吗
How do you...
你怎么能...
Maybe you're estranged because your husband
也许你疏远你丈夫是因为他
left you saddled with hundreds of thousands of dollars in debt.
让你承担了数十万美元的债务
Gambling, right?
赌博 对吧
I don't know what this is. You're underwater,
-我不知道这是什么 -你被紧紧套牢
desperate for money,
极渴望得到钱
so when Parsa approached you,
所以当Parsa接近你
he didn't have to threaten you, like you claimed.
他并不需要威胁你 就像你声称的那样
He just bribed you.
他只需收买你
Had to be a lot to betray your country.
他肯定是花了一大笔钱使你背叛你的国家
And Petty Officer Coyne.
至于上士Coyne
You told Parsa Coyne was involved in the drone attack
你告诉Parsa Coyne参与了无人机空袭
and took out his compound.
干掉他的大本营
You basically signed his death warrant.
你基本上相当于判了他的死刑
Since you've looked at my correspondence
既然你已经看过我的通信
and my finances, you know I haven't received
和财务状况 那你就应该知道我没收到过
a penny from anyone.
任何人一分钱
Tell us about Palm Ridge.
跟我们说说Palm Ridge
It's the assisted-living facility where my sister is.
那是我妹妹所在的生活辅助机构
She was hurt... in a car accident in college.
她受伤了...上大学时发生了一场车祸
Traumatic brain injury. She's been there ever since.
是脑外伤 从那时起她就一直在那
Your parents set up a trust
你的父母为支付照顾她的生活费用
to take care of her living expenses.
建立了一个信托
You're the executor. And three days ago,
-你是遗嘱执行人 - 三天前
that trust received an infusion of cash-- $5 million.
那个信托收到现金 5百万
Now, listen, Erin,
现在 听着 Erin
either your sister...
要么是你妹妹...
in her catatonic state, somehow colluded with Benham Parsa
在精神分裂的状况下 不知何故与Benham Parsa勾结
to commit high treason, or...
犯叛国罪 要么就是...
You did.
你做的
They beat me, you know.
他们打我 你知道
Tied me up.
把我绑起来
- I'm a victim. - No.
-我是受害者 -不
No, Daniel Coyne is a victim.
不 Daniel Coyne才是受害者
Whoever else has been targeted is a victim.
不管是谁 被攻击的目标才是受害者
You're a terrorist,
你只是个恐怖分子
and you're gonna serve 50 years in federal prison.
而且你将在联邦监狱服刑50年
Minimum.
至少
They're incredible...
它们真是难以置信...
...these weapons I've helped build.
...我帮助建造的这些武器
You sit behind a computer monitor,
你坐在一个电脑显示器前
point, click and...
点击 然后...
thousands of miles away, total destruction.
数千里外 彻底毁灭
Parsa thinks it's only fair we get a taste.
Parsa认为 只有让我们也体会一下 才是公平的
The drone's been loaded with a hundred pounds
无人机装载着 一百磅
of C-4 explosives. It's out there now.
C-4炸弹 现在就在外面
Erin Pace doesn't know the target.
Erin Pace不知道目标
Could be lying. No, no. Parsa
她可能在撒谎 不 不 Parsa
wanted us to catch her; it was part of his plan.
希望我们抓到她 这是他计划的一部分
He kept her in the dark intentionally. We need to find him.
他故意让她陷入黑暗 -我们需要找到他
There's a second team at NSA helping the FBI
NSA的第二支队伍正在帮助FBI
run a high-frequency trace on any unexplained radio signals.
搜寻任何高频率异常无线电信号的痕迹
- We will. - Not in time.
-我们会的 -赶不上了
What's his target?
他的目标是什么
He wants revenge, right?
他想复仇 对吗
For taking out his training camp.
因为我们干掉了他的训练营
The Pentagon? Military bases?
五角大楼 军事基地
Parsa's targets are symbolic-- he doesn't want to just...
Parsa的目标是象征性的 而不是仅仅...
take out some soldiers. Bishop...
-干掉几个士兵 -Bishop...
what is he thinking?
他是怎么想的
The people that he kills have meaning--
他杀的人都是有意义的
like-like Coyne, who helped take out his compound in Pakistan.
就像Coyne 参与干掉了他在巴基斯坦的大本营
Call McGee. The Conrad gala.
-打电话给McGee  -Conrad晚宴
Half the counterterrorism community is there tonight.
今晚那里有一半的反恐组织
People who have been hunting Parsa for years.
多年来一直在追捕Parsa的人
Call McGee.
打电话给McGee
Tony, you know, I figured
Tony 你知道 我就知道
you'd try and upstage my one night off.
你想抢走我一晚上的休息时间
What?
什么
Wait, hold on. What is it?
-等等 等一下 -什么情况
I don't know. I can't hear.
我不知道 我听不清楚
Um, I'll meet you inside?
嗯 我到里面找你
Okay? Okay.
-好吗 -好的
Tony, what's going on?
Tony 发生什么事
Parsa's drone wasn't destroyed.
Parsa的无人机没有被破坏
He's using it on the Conrad gala.
它将袭击Conrad晚宴
Homeland and Metro are on their way.
国土安全局和特区警署已经在路上了
Get everyone out there, right now!
让所有人离开那里 马上
SIGINT team's got a hit on the radio frequency...
通信情报部门通过高频率无线电捕捉到一次袭击
Oh, my God.
哦 上帝啊
Gibbs, are you there?
Gibbs 你还在吗
Bishop, give me the address.
Bishop 给我地址
Okay. Okay, stand by.
好的 好的 待命
Are we going to McGee?
我们是去McGee那吗
No. We get Parsa.
不 我们找到Parsa了
Federal agents!
联邦探员
Benham Parsa!
Benham Parsa
Hands above your head!
举手放头上
Hey. I'm escorting Erin Pace to Federal Detention.
嘿 我护送Erin Pace去联邦拘留所
I was hoping I'd see you before I left. Don't be a stranger.
-我希望在我离开之前能再见你 -别那么见外
You keep that bottle in a safe place.
把那瓶酒放在安全的地方
Someday we'll finish it. And, Jethro...
有一天我们会将它喝完 最后 Jethro...
You'll get him; you always do.
你会抓到他的 你一直如此
Hey, I just came from the scene.
嘿 我刚从现场回来
McGee's okay. He wasn't in the hotel when the drone hit.
McGee没事 无人机袭击时他并不在酒店里
Casualties? Four dead so far.
伤亡情况 到目前为止四个人
More than a few dozen wounded.
十几人受伤
Delilah?
Delilah呢
She was hit with a lot of shrapnel.
她被许多弹片击伤了
She's in surgery. They're doing what they can.
她在手术室 他们在尽最大的努力
- Should we go to the hospital? - No.
-我们可以去医院吗 -不
No, we should find Parsa. How?
-不能 我们应该找到Parsa -怎么做
You start at the beginning, Bishop.
从最初开始 Bishop
Come on.
快点
This is what you do.
这就是你要做的
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
快点 快点 快点 快点
Bishop.
Bishop
Come on!
快点
All right, get to work.
好的 开始工作
You find him.
你要找到他
Get this son of a bitch.
找到这个狗娘养的